

HAROLD FRIEDMAN Counsel

LITIGATION GROUP DIVORCE & FAMILY LAW GROUP 1100 Valley Brook Avenue P.O. Box 790 Lyndhurst, NJ 07071-0790 Phone: 201-806-3432 Fax: 201-806-3480 hfriedman@sh-law.com

BIOGRAPHY

Harold Friedman, counsel to the firm, has over 50 years of extensive experience in the legal profession. Mr. Friedman, admitted to the State Bar of New Jersey (1960), and a graduate of Yale Law School (1959) and Yale University (Magna cum laude, 1956), is well versed in a broad range of civil law practices.

Mr. Friedman has assisted large corporate, business clients and insurance carriers with a wide variety of complex business transactions and commercial litigation and appeals, including those dealing with business break-ups, unfair trade practice, business torts and insurance defense matters. Mr. Friedman also has represented governmental and municipal entities as well as individuals in handling their litigation in contractual, business, environmental, real estate, product liability, estate and matrimonial and divorce matters.

EDUCATION

- Yale Law School (L.L.B. 1959)
- Yale University (B.A., magna cum laude, 1956)

BAR ADMISSIONS

- New Jersey (1960)
- U.S. Supreme Court (1970)
- U.S. Court of Appeals, Third Circuit
- U.S. Court of Appeals, Tenth Circuit
- U.S. District Court, District of New Jersey
- U.S. District Court, Southern District of New York
- U.S. District Court, Eastern District of New York

AFFILIATIONS

- New Jersey State Bar Association (General Counsel, 1980-1981)
- Hudson County Bar Association

PUBLICATIONS

Author: "The Bankruptcy Preference Challenge to After-Acquired Property Clauses Under the Code, "108 University of Pennsylvania Law Review 941, December, 1959

OTHER EXPERIENCE

- Member and Chairman New Jersey Supreme Court District Fee Arbitration Committee (1979-1983; 1987-1990)
- Adjunct Professor of Law, Rutgers Law School (Newark)





